我们就在那里
So there we were,
在沙漠里艰难行军
scraping our sacks in the sandbox.
沙丘之上的活靶子
Open targets in the dunes.
我们都在流汗咒骂
All of us sweating and swearing.
总比坐在方圆三十公里内荒无人烟的地方
Sure as hell beat sitting on our asses 30 clicks to nowhere
等待有驼峰的朋友
waiting for our humpbacked friend
拉出车钥匙要好
to defecate the keys to our transport.
骆驼不吃钥匙
Camels don't eat keys.
吃的  它吃了
They do, it did.
而且拉出来了
And it shit it out.
不骗你
I shit you not.
你是个傻瓜
You're an idiot.
我从来没否认过
I've never denied it.
美好新世界
Brave new world.
我还是一直在想玛姬怀孕的事
I still can't stop thinking about Maggie having a pup.
在这种情况下
In this.
怎么了
What about it?
现在这种情况
You know, the way things go.
什么坏事都有可能发生
The way they can.
是啊
Yeah.
也许这就是原因
Maybe that's why.
因为现在这种情况
Because the way things go.
你已经说我是傻瓜了
You already called me an idiot.
我开玩笑的
Never had to.
好吧
Yeah.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
不
Nope.
我
I'm, uh,
要重新排班了
starting a new shift.
巴格里那边的岗哨
The watch post on baggarly.
是吗
That so?
我和尤金谈过了
Yeah, I already talked to Eugene.
他想帮更多的忙
He wants to help out more.
他说他会代替我跟你巡逻
Said he'd take over my patrol with you.
太好了
How about that?
-是啊  -是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
太好了
How about that?
回头见吧
See you around?
好
Yeah.
回头见  亚伯拉罕
See you around, Abraham.
亚伯拉罕
Hey, Abraham.
你还好吗
You're still here?
你知道尤金要开始巡逻了吗
You know Eugene's gonna start patrolling?
他让我教他怎么拆自动手枪
He asked me to teach him how to fieldstrip automatics.
他要教我化学
He's gonna teach me chemistry.
化学没法教
You can't teach chemistry.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Mm-mm.
我的天啊
Sweet flaming mercy.
那真是太棒了
That was just... beyond.
是吗
Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah?
接住了
Catch.
是油罐车上的
It's from the fuel truck.
我打碎了一个刹车灯
Had to crack a brake light.
这是你做的吗
You made this?
我觉得你的脖子看起来有些孤独
Thought your neck looked a little lonely.
罗西塔·埃斯皮诺萨
Rosita Espinosa,
你真是太完美了  知道吗
you are damn near perfection, you know that?
戴上给我看看
Show me.
去浴室
In the shower.
马上去
In a minute.
玛姬
Maggie.
我们搭好棚架  就能垂直种植了
We get the trellises in, we can start going vertically.
每平方英尺的西红柿产量能翻番
Double our yield of tomatoes per square foot.
定量配给撑不了太久
We can only keep stretching our rations so far.
还是没看见一颗小芽
Still haven't seen a single bud.
亲爱的
Babe.
会长出来的
It'll grow.
我们会没事的
We're gonna be okay.
你在我们家里做什么
What the hell are you doing in our house?
我坐在台阶上
I'm, uh, sitting on the steps
看着这幅画
looking at this painting,
等着你爸妈穿好衣服
Waiting for your mom and dad to get dressed.
我是耶稣
I'm Jesus.
卡尔
Carl, hey, um...
没事
It's-- it's okay.
你说了我们该谈谈
You said we should talk.
那就谈吧
So let's talk.
你怎么逃出来的
So, how'd you get out?
一个守卫看不住两个出口
One guard can't cover two exits
或者三楼的窗户
or third floor windows.
解开绳结  撬开锁
Knots untie and locks get picked.
-熵来源于秩序  对吧  -对
- Entropy comes from order, right? - Right.
我查看了你们的武器库
I checked out your arsenal.
很久没有见过这么多武器了
I haven't seen anything like that in a long time.
你们装备精良  但是食物不足
You're well-equipped, but your provisions are low.
不够你们这么多人吃
Very low for the amount of people you have.
-54个吗  -更多
- 54? - More than that.
饼干很好吃
Well, I appreciate the cookie.
厨师手艺不错
My compliments to the chef.
她不在
Yeah, she ain't here.
我们开局不顺
Look, we got off to a bad start.
但我们是站在同一边的  生存的那一边
But we're on the same side-- the living side.
你和瑞克完全可以丢下我
You and Rick had every reason to leave me out there,
但你们没有
but you didn't.
我来自的地方和这里很像
I'm from a place that's a lot like this one.
我的工作之一就是寻找其他可以做交易的营地
Part of my job is searching out other settlements to trade with.
我开走了你们的车
I took your truck because
是因为我的社区需要东西
my community needs things,
而你俩看起来都不像好人
and both of you looked like trouble.
我错了
I was wrong.
你们是好人
You're good people.
这里是个好地方
And this is a good place.
我觉得我们两边可以互相帮助
I think our communities may be in a position to help each other.
你们有食物吗
Do you have food?
我们饲养牲畜
We've started to raise livestock.
寻找补给  种地
We scavenge, we grow.
从西红柿到高粱应有尽有
Everything from tomatoes to sorghum.
告诉我们为什么要相信你
Tell us why we should believe you.
我可以带你们去看
I'll show you.
如果我们开车  一天内就能回我家
If we take a car, I can take you back home in a day,
你们可以自己看看
and you can all see for yourselves
我们是什么人  可以提供什么
who we are and what we have to offer.
等等  你在寻找更多营地
Wait, you're looking for more settlements.
意思是你们已经和别的团体交易了吗
You mean you're already trading with other groups?
你们的世界即将变得更广阔
Your world's about to get a whole lot bigger.
《行尸走肉》
给  自制的燕麦蛋糕
Homemade oat cake.
复合碳水化合物  含有欧米伽3脂肪酸
Complex carbohydrates, omega-3s.
不  我不要
Nah, I'm good.
我们路上要停车  到时候我再找吃的
We're gonna make a pit stop. I'll pick up something then.
你想染上狂犬病吗
Like rabies?
这是因为我想给你弄到汽水吗
Is this 'cause I tried to get you that stuff?
是的
Yeah.
还有你让我想到了我以前认识的某人
And you remind me of someone I used to know.
好吧
Well...
希望要比看起来好吃
I hope it tastes better than it looks.
因为看起来跟屎一样
'Cause it looks like shit.
屎也比路上的死动物要好
Shit's still better than roadkill.
好吧  也许  吃了吧
Okay, maybe-- just eat it.
你确定吗
You sure?
不
No.
但如果他说的是真话
But if he's telling the truth,
这可能是新生活的开始
this could be the start of everything.
我打算跟你说我和米琼恩的事
Look, I was gonna tell you about me and Michonne,
但这事刚发生
but it just happened.
这事刚发生
It just happened.
就在昨晚
Last night.
这次不一样
This is-- this is different.
没事
It's cool.
好吧
All right.
拿上你的东西
Well, get your stuff.
我们离开时加百利能照顾朱迪思
Gabriel can take care of Judith while we're gone.
我不去
No, I'm not coming.
得有人留在家里  保护这里
Someone's gotta stay back, keep this place safe.
反正一个毁了容的小孩八成也不能
A kid with a messed-up face probably wouldn't make
给人留下多好的第一印象
the best first impression anyway.
我们上路吧
Let's chew up some asphalt!
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
当然
Sure.
当你倒松饼粉时
When you were, uh, pouring the bisquick,
你是想做松饼吗(暗示怀孕)
were you trying to make pancakes?
是的吧
Yes?
我懂了
Oh, okay, um...
我们之前谈论过
It's something that we talked about, yeah.
-是啊  -为什么问
- Yeah. - Why?
没什么  我只是...
No, I just...
在这种朝不保夕的情况下
Well, given the precarious state of affairs on any given Sunday,
我他妈真的是被你们这些有胆量
I am damn near floored that you or anyone else
做出这种决定的人吓到了
would have the cojones to make a call like that.
我...
I mean, well...
我们试图营造一些东西  我和她
we're trying to build something, me and her.
我们所有人
All of us.
声明一下
For the record,
我一旦看到要下雨  就会穿胶鞋
I see rain coming, I'm wearing galoshes.
我穿两双
I double up.
瑞克  怎么了
Yo, Rick. What's going on?
前面出车祸了
We got a crash ahead.
看着像是刚刚发生的
Looks like it just happened.
是我们的人
It's one of ours.
假如这是个陷阱  你不会有好下场的
If this is a trick, it won't end well for you.
我的人遇到麻烦了
My people are in trouble.
他们不...  我们之中没有多少战士
They don't-- we don't have a lot of fighters.
我知道这看起来有诈  但我会乖乖的
I know how it looks, but I'll play it out.
能借我一把枪吗
Can I borrow a gun?
不行
No.
这里有痕迹
We got tracks right here.
他们一定是在里面
They gotta be in there.
我们是进去还是怎样
We moving in or what?
我们怎么知道这会不会是陷阱
How do we know this ain't firecrackers in a trash can?
你们不知道
You don't.
我们会把你的人救出来
We'll get your people.
你和我们中的一个留在这里
You're staying here with one of us.
这是条件
That's the deal.
-你留下好吗  -好的
- Will you stay? - Yeah.
你们去吧  千万小心
Y'all go. Just be careful.
好的
Yeah.
我们会很小心的
We're gonna be careful.
快点吧
Just hurry.
我一吹口哨  你就杀了他
You hear me whistle, shoot him.
我会的
I will.
出来吧  我们不会伤害你们
Come on out. We're not gonna hurt you.
我们是耶稣的朋友
We're friends of Jesus.
我们是来救你们出去的
We're here to get you out.
还有人吗
There more of you?
还有两个  他们跑到前面去了
Two more. They ran ahead.
来吧
Come on.
我们是耶稣的朋友  走吧
We're with Jesus. Let's go.
我不能和你们走  我在找我的朋友
I can't go with you. I'm looking for my friend.
他就在附近  还在车祸中受了伤
He's close, and he's hurt from the crash.
不
No!
快  伙计  我们撤
Come on, man, let's go.
走吧
Come on!
-扶住了吗  -走
- You got him? - Go.
走吧  走吧
Come on. Come on.
顺便说句  我叫哈兰
Name's Harlan, by the way.
玛姬
Maggie.
那是我丈夫  格伦
That's my husband, Glenn.
我们正要把药品带回去
We're bringing back medication,
所以你救下的人可能不止我们  格伦
so you may have saved more people than just us back there, Glenn.
你是医生吗
You're a doctor?
是的  没错
Yeah, that's right.
你那里有孕期维生素吗
You have any prenatal vitamins in there?
给你用的
For you?
我之前是妇产科医生
Well, uh, I was an obstetrician before,
而且我绝对欠你们人情
and I most definitely owe you.
所以  我会说你们俩中了头彩
So, I'd say you two just hit the jackpot.
你还好吗  弗莱迪
You okay, Freddie?
刚才
For a second back there,
当我以为他就要...
just when I thought he was gonna...
我看到了我妻子
I saw my wife.
灾变之前她就去世了
She died before all this.
正当我以为我死定了的时候
Just when I thought it was over,
我看到了她
there she was.
一清二楚
Clear as day.
该死
Damn it.
肯定是刚下过暴风雨
A storm must've passed through.
我们被困住了
We're stuck.
别担心
No worries.
已经到了
We're here.
就在那
That's us.
那就是山顶寨
That's the Hilltop.
站住
Stop right there.
你想逼我们停吗
You gonna make us?
耶稣  这是怎么回事
Jesus, what the hell is this?
把门打开  卡奥
Open the gates, Cal.
弗莱迪受伤了
Freddie's hurt.
听着  我为他们道歉
Look, sorry about these guys.
他们一整天站在那里无所事事  有点焦躁
They get antsy standing up there all day doing nothing.
他们必须交出武器  然后我们才会开门
They give up the weapons. Then we'll open the gates.
你干嘛不下来自己拿
Why don't you come down here and get 'em?
先生们  我们为这些人担保  好吗
Gentlemen, look, we vouch for these people, all right?
是他们救了我们
They saved us out there.
别举着矛了
Lower the spears.
听着  我可不想冒险
Look, I'm not taking any chances.
-还是让那位格雷戈里出来吧  -不
- Tell your guy Gregory to come out here.- No.
你没看到刚发生了什么吗
Don't you see what just happened?
我同意你们保留武器
I'm letting you keep your guns.
听着  几个月前我们就没有弹药了
Look, we ran out of ammo months ago.
我挺喜欢你们的
I like you people.
我相信你们
I trust you.
也请相信我们
Trust us.
开门  卡奥
Open the gates, Cal.
再次感谢
Thanks again.
随时可以来找我
Come see me whenever.
我就在医疗拖车里  好吗
I'm just over here in the medical trailer, okay?
好
Ok.
这曾是附近一家电力公司的材料场
There was a materials yard for a power company nearby.
所以我们才能建起高墙
That's how we put up the walls.
很多人都是从应急营地来的
A lot of people came from a FEMA camp.
他们带来了拖车
Trailers came with them.
人们是怎么找到这里的
How did people find out about this place?
那地方叫巴林顿公馆
That's called Barrington House.
三十年代  这家的主人把它捐给了州里
The family that owned it gave it to the state in the '30s.
州里又把它改造成了生活史博物馆
The state turned it into a Living History Museum.
五十英里内的所有小学
Every elementary school for
都让学生来这里参观过
50 miles used to come here for field trips.
现代社会建立之前
The place was running a long time
它就已经运转了很长时间
before the modern world built up around it.
我想人们之所以会来  是因为
I think people came here because
他们想着现代社会毁灭之后它仍会继续
they figured it'd keep running after the modern world broke down.
我们可以从那些窗户看到数英里之外的各个方向
Those windows up there let us see for miles in every direction.
能保证安全
It's perfect for security.
来吧  我带你们看看里面
Come on. I'll show you inside.
我的老天爷啊
Good gracious, Ignatius.
多数房间已经被改造成起居室了
Most of the rooms have been converted to living spaces.
就连曾经不是卧房的也改了
Even the ones that weren't bedrooms.
人们住在这里和拖车里
People live here and the trailers?
我们还计划多建些房屋
We plan to build.
有孩子在这里出生
There's babies being born.
耶稣
Jesus.
你回来了
You're back.
还带了客人
With guests.
各位  这位是格雷戈里
Everyone, this is Gregory.
他让这里正常运转
He keeps the trains running on time around here.
我是头儿
I'm the boss.
我叫瑞克  我们有个社区...
Well, I'm Rick. We have a community...
你们为何不去清理一下
Why don't y'all go get cleaned up?
不用了
We're fine.
耶稣会带你们去洗澡的地方
Jesus will show you where you can get washed up.
搞干净了再下来
Then come back down here when you're ready.
这地方不容易保洁
It's hard to keep this place clean.
好的  可以
Yeah. Sure.
跟我来
Follow me.
你先洗  你跟他谈
You clean up first. You talk to him.
为什么
Why?
不该我来
I shouldn't.
你也要开始和人谈判了
And you gotta start doing these things.
你觉得瑞克和米琼恩搞在一起多长时间了
How long do you think Rick and Michonne been ugging bumplies?
不知道
I don't know.
你想过吗
You ever think about it?
安定下来
Settling down?
你觉得有可能安定吗
You think shit's settled?
格雷戈里
Gregory.
-娜塔莉是吗  -是玛姬
- Natalie, right? - Maggie.
没啥区别
That's pretty close.
还是有的
Not really.
有一说一  我喜欢
She calls them like she sees them. I like that.
请进  我们谈谈
Come in, let's chat.
好了
Yeah.
我以前来过这里一次
I-- I came to this place once before,
那时还是个博物馆
when it was a museum,
因为商会的事
this, um, Chamber of Commerce thing.
我喜欢这幅画
Love that painting.
我从没想过会是我的
I never figured it'd be mine,
但现在就在眼前
here it is.
就像它一直在等着我一样
It's like it was waiting for me the whole time.
耶稣告诉我  你们救了卡森医生
Jesus told me your group saved Dr. Carson.
显然现如今医生是稀缺资源了
Obviously, a doctor's a rare commodity today,
所以感谢你们带他回来
so I want to thank you for bringing ours back.
是我丈夫救了他
My husband saved him.
也同样感谢他
I'll be sure to thank him, too.
你拥有的这地方
This place, what you have here,
-一开始就这样吗  -没错
- has been here since the start? -That's right.
那你们是怎么活下来的
And how-- how is it-- how have you survived here?
就像这样  只能说我擅长此道
You're looking at how. I'm good at this.
而且我不拘泥于细节
And I don't get hung up on the details.
你们住的地方和山顶寨一样好吗
Where you live, is it as nice as the Hilltop Colony?
不一样
It's just different.
你怎么保证食物供给
How do you feed everyone?
耶稣说你们有菜园  但没有庄稼
Jesus said you had land for gardens, but no crops.
我们才开始种植
We just started planting.
-种什么  -黄瓜  西红柿
- Planting what? - Cucumbers, tomatoes.
庄稼指的是大豆  玉米  麻类  高粱
Oh, crops-- soy, corn, hemp, sorghum.
-我们种蔬果  -但你们有枪
- Garden stuff. - But you have guns,
我猜你们有不少武器库存
so I assume you have a decent weapons cache.
确实不少
It's decent.
那你们的医务室  医疗用品充足吗
And your infirmary, is it stocked?
你们的充足吗
Is yours?
我们是来谈交易的
We came here hoping to talk trade.
你有足够的资源吗
Do you have enough here for that?
你能看到我有什么
You see what I have here.
你能看到我建立了什么
You see what I've built.
耶稣说你们的食物状况不容乐观
Jesus said that your food situation was challenged right now.
如果人们吃不饱  一切就会崩溃
You don't keep people fed, it comes apart.
别绕弯子了好吗
Let's speak the common tongue here, huh?
你们屁都没有
You don't have shit.
我很乐意帮忙  我是个好人
Now, I'm happy to help. I'm a nice guy.
但我们不能白给
But we can't just give things away for free.
不如这样
How's this?
既然你们没什么物资
Since you can't offer much,
我就让你们的人在这里用劳动交换
I'll let your people work here for their share.
这个社区很欢迎你这样的人
You'd be a welcome addition to the community,
一位聪明美丽的女士
a smart and beautiful woman.
话说回来
Getting back to that common tongue,
我告诉你  我会让你觉得物超所值的
I can tell ya, I can make it worth your while.
-给我打住  -听着  亲爱的
- Let me stop you right there. - Listen, honey.
不要叫我亲爱的来骚扰我
Stop coming on to me with calling me honey.
你们一点弹药都没有
You don't have any ammunition.
谁说的
Who said that?
你们药物不足
You're low on medication.
我们双方都有需要的东西
You need things. We need things.
所以你们要给我们一瓶阿司匹林和一盒子弹吗
What, are you gonna give us a bottle of aspirin and a box of bullets?
我们两个社区能互相帮助
Our communities can help each other.
谢谢  娜塔莉  谈得很愉快
Thank you, Natalie. Been a good talk.
我们能互相帮助
We can help each other.
我们现在过得挺好
We're doing fine.
你们呢
Are you?
我们想要交易  格雷戈里想要交易
We want to generate trade. Gregory does.
但是子弹不是我们迫切所需的
But ammo isn't something we urgently need.
-为什么  -墙还能撑着
- Well, how's that? - The walls hold.
我们刚带回来了更多药物
We just brought in more medicine.
格雷戈里想要最好的交易
Gregory wants the best deal possible.
我们也有想要的东西
Yeah, well, we want things, too.
我们需要食物
We need food.
我们大老远来  必须拿到
We came all this way, we're gonna get it.
我会跟他谈
I will talk to him
我们能解决的
and we will work this out.
情况变了
Circumstances change.
我们现在过得不错  你们以后也会的
We're doing well now, and you will next.
我会让他理解这点
I will make him understand that.
能再给我几天时间吗
Can you give me a few days?
可以
We can.
好的
Yeah.
出什么事了
What's wrong?
他们回来了
They're back.
内森  其他人呢
Nathan, what happened to everybody else?
蒂姆和玛莎呢
Where's Tim and Marsha?
他们死了
They're dead.
-尼根干的吗  -是的
- Negan? - Yeah.
-我们有约在先的  -他说那不够
- We had a deal. - He said it wasn't enough.
贡品少了吗
Was the drop light?
没有
No.
克雷格还在他们手上
They still have Craig.
他们说会留他一命  把他还给我们
They said they'd keep him alive, return him to us,
只要我给你带个信
if I deliver a message to you.
说吧
So, tell me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
放开我  我必须这么做
Get off of me! I had to!
也许这就是原因
Maybe that's why.
因为现在这种情况
Because the way things go.
住手
Hey!
退后  谁拦着我
Stay back! Anybody who tries to stop me
就是想害死我兄弟
is killing my brother!
放下
Drop it.
怎么了
What?
内森  你杀了他
Nathan! You killed him.
他想杀格雷戈里  然后杀我
He tried to kill Gregory, then me.
别
Don't.
放下武器
Drop it now!
我觉得我不会
I don't think I will.
大家听着  都结束了
Everyone, this is over!
结束了
It's over.
内森是我们的朋友  但别忘了
Nathan was our friend, but let's not pretend
他也是想袭击我们的懦夫
he was anything more than a coward who attacked us.
是他起的头
He did this.
而这些人制止了他
And these people stopped him.
我该怎么做
What can I do?
把枪拿开
Put the gun away.
你做的够多了
You've done enough.
你得知道
You need to know
事情没你想象的那么简单
that things aren't as simple as they might seem.
给我点时间
Just give me some time.
老兄
Hey, man.
你还好吧
You good?
是啊
Yeah.
我好得很
I'm better than all right.
卡森医生帮格雷戈里包扎了伤口
Dr. Carson was able to patch Gregory up.
他现在很痛苦  但还活着
He's in pain, but he'll live.
现在怎么办
So, what happens now?
这种事很少在这里发生
Things like that don't usually happen here,
但是已经解决了
but, uh, it's settled.
我们听到了尼根的名字
We heard the name Negan.
之前达里尔和亚伯拉罕跟他的人起过冲突
A while back, Daryl and Abraham had a run-in with his men.
他是谁
Who is he?
尼根领导着一群他所谓的救世军
Negan's the head of a group of people he calls the Saviors.
墙造好以后  救世军就出现了
As soon as the walls were built, the Saviors showed up.
他们代表他们的老大见了格雷戈里
They met with Gregory on behalf of their boss.
他们提出了很多要求  做出了更多威胁
They made a lot of demands, even more threats.
他杀了我们其中一员  罗里
And he killed one of us-- Rory.
他才16岁
He was 16 years old.
他们当着我们的面  把他活活打死了
They beat him to death right in front of us.
他说我们必须明白局势
Said we needed to understand, right off the bat.
格雷戈里不是很擅长处理冲突
Gregory's not exactly good at confrontation.
他不是我心中的领导人选
He's not the leader I would've chosen,
但是他帮我们创建了这个地方
but he helped make this place what it is,
大家都很喜欢他
and the people like him.
他接受了条件
He made the deal.
全部的一半
Half of everything.
我们的补给  我们的作物
Our supplies, our crops,
我们的牲畜  一半都给救世军
our livestock, it goes to the Saviors.
你们能得到什么作为交换
And what do you get in return?
他们不会攻击这里
They don't attack this place.
他们不会杀了我们
They don't kill us.
为什么不能杀了他们
Why not just kill them?
这儿大多数人都不知道怎么战斗
Most of the people here don't even know how to fight,
即使我们有弹药
even if we had ammo.
尼根手下有多少人
Well, how many people does Negan have?
我们不知道
We don't know.
我们最多见过二十个人
We've seen groups as big as 20.
等等  他们就这么出现  杀了一个孩子
Now, hold up. So, they show up, they kill a kid,
你们就乖乖奉上一半物资吗
and you give them half of everything?
这群混蛋只是在编故事
These dicks just got a good story.
吓小孩的  他没什么了不起
The bogeyman, he ain't shit.
你怎么能确定
Well, how do you know?
一个月前  我们轻松干掉了他们的人
A month ago, we took his guys out PDQ.
把他们打得七零八落
Left them in pieces and puddles.
我们会帮你的
You know, we'll do it.
如果我们救回你的人
If we go get your man back,
杀死尼根  干掉他的人
kill Negan, take out his boys,
你能帮我们吗
will you hook us up?
我们要食物  药品  和一头奶牛
We want food, medicine, and one of them cows.
我们从来不怕处理冲突
Confrontation's never been something we've had trouble with.
我会告诉格雷戈里的
I'll take it to Gregory.
他们有食物  我们没有
They have food, we don't.
我们什么都不够
We don't have enough of anything.
我们只有我们自己
Except us.
和我们能做到的事
What we can do.
这就是交易
This is the trade.
我们也会付出代价的
It's gonna cost us something.
格雷戈里起来了  他想谈谈
Gregory's up. He wants to talk.
和玛姬
To Maggie.
他想和玛姬谈谈
He wants to talk to Maggie.
你可以的
You got this.
迪安娜对你的看法没有错
Deanna was right about you.
事先先向你道个歉  格雷戈里有时很混蛋
I'm sorry in advance. Gregory can be a real prick.
我知道
I know.
进来
Come in.
抱歉房间里很暗
Sorry for the gloom.
他们给我注射了抗生素
They have me on these antibiotics
让我对光线很敏感
that make me sensitive to the sunlight.
实在是太痛苦了
This is agony.
好像有人在用水泥搅拌机搅我的肠胃
It's like somebody's twisting my intestines with a cement mixer.
本可能会更糟
It could've been worse.
我们在这儿算你走运
You're lucky we were here.
耶稣跟你说了我们的条件吗
Jesus told you about our offer?
是的
He did.
你们凭什么认为能做到我们做不到的事
What makes you think you can do what we haven't done?
我们对付过尼根这样的人
We've handled people like Negan.
-怎么对付  -他们已经死了
- How? - They're dead.
我们能救回你们的人
We can get your man back.
真不知道克雷格值不值得这样大费周折
I don't know if Craig's worth the trouble.
毕竟这是他兄弟做的
I mean, it's his brother who did this.
他是为了救他所爱的人
He was fighting to save someone he loves.
他很害怕
He was afraid.
那令他软弱
That makes him weak.
说实话  我不知道我是否想让他回到这里
Frankly, I don't know if I want him back in our gene pool.
我爸爸曾告诉我
My dad used to tell me
原谅比愤怒更需要勇气
forgiveness takes more strength than anger.
也许是吧
Yeah, I guess.
他是个很好的厨师
He's a hell of a cook.
他做的青西红柿烤蛋非常好吃
He makes these amazing baked eggs with green tomatoes.
你给我们物资  我们去救克雷格
You give us supplies, we'll save Craig
灭掉尼根和救世军
and take care of Negan and the Saviors, permanently.
抱歉  我觉得这段对话很可笑
I'm sorry, I find this whole conversation pretty funny.
我提出让你们劳动换物资时
I mean, you balked when I proposed
你犹豫了  但是现在
that your people work for our supplies, but now...
结果不是完全一样吗
isn't that exactly what's happening here?
我有筹码  我利用了
See, I had leverage and I used it.
瞧  这不是针对你
See? It wasn't personal.
是的
Yes.
我们需要食物  你们有食物
We need food. You have it.
我们愿意用劳动交换
We're willing to work for it.
那我会给你们的人准备物资
Then I'll get supplies for your people.
很好
Good.
我会跟耶稣谈谈  做好安排
I'll talk to Jesus and he'll make the arrangements.
瞧  这挺有趣的
See, this was fun.
令人激动
Exciting.
一半
Half.
什么
Excuse me?
全部的一半
Half of what you have.
我看到在外面发生了什么
I saw what happened out there.
尼根想要这里进贡更多物资
Negan's expecting more supplies from this place.
而且会越来越多
And more and more.
如果继续下去
And if it keeps going like that,
你们很快会一无所有
pretty soon you won't have anything left.
然后会发生什么
What happens then?
没有弹药  没有战士
Without ammo, without fighters...
你就死定了
you'd be a dead man.
所以我要你们一半的物资
So half of everything you have
现在就要
right now
否则交易取消
or the deal's off.
瞧
You see?
我有筹码
I have leverage.
恭喜
Congratulations.
交易达成
You have yourself a deal.
你还要什么  要一个肾吗
You want anything else? Kidney, maybe?
不用了
Not that...
但我的确想要一样东西
but I do want something.
连尼根第一次都没拿走这么多
Even Negan didn't get this much up front.
什么事
What?
耶稣说你从一开始
Jesus said you've been
就负责给尼根运送物资
taking supplies to Negan since the beginning.
我们会救回克雷格
We're gonna get Craig back.
救回克雷格的唯一方式是
The only way to get Craig back
献上格雷戈里的人头
is to bring them Gregory's head.
我们会救回克雷格
We're gonna get Craig back.
怎么救
How?
我们需要你提供尼根基地的情报
We need to know what you know about Negan's compound.
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
我们需要你一起走
We need you to come.
好
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
还能坐下一个人吗
You got room for one more, right?
我们可是要去让世界恢复正义
I mean, we're talking about righting the world here.
再说了  我的刀还在你们那里
Plus, you still have my knives.
你准备好了吗
Hey, you up for this?
肯定会战斗的
It's gonna be a fight.
我们会赢的
We'll win.
我们必须赢
We have to.
我们会赢的
We'll win.